Hello everyone and welcome to the computer vision of Python an open C-v course and this lecture going
to have a quick course overview.
I have a favor to ask of you and it's Please don't skip this lecture.
I know a lot of times people want to jump ahead to the really cool material but it's going to be a few
housekeeping items that are really important to the Course here.
So if you've taken other courses of mine before please don't skip this lecture.
There's a few important points that are different than other courses.
OK.
So to quickly go over everything we're going to talk about.
Useful Tips for going through the course how to get help during the course.
Some advice how to approach the course or to find the actual course notebooks and code and how to use
the student chat channel.
So a couple of useful tips right off the bat.
I tend to speak at a pretty steady pace.
However maybe English isn't your first language so you want to slow down the videos or you actually
prefer to watch videos at a higher speed like I do.
You can use the video player settings at the bottom of your video player to speed up or slow down the
videos.
If you want to download the videos you can use the Official you Timmy app to do so.
Also please make sure to make use of her question answer forums.
There's lots of previous discussion available there.
Since we have thousands of students now let's talk about getting help.
If you have any issue with things that are platform level those are things like issues of video play
back or logging in getting your actual certification for the course or issues with payments or sales
discounts.
Please e-mail support you to me dot com.
Those are you to me platform level issues and we actually don't have control over that.
So the best way to get help is to email support at me dot com or to directly open a support ticket with
them.
Now let's talk about getting help in regards to the Course material.
A couple of quick tips is you should always double check against the course note books that we provide
and it's always a good idea to do a quick google or stack overflow search.
Often if you just Google search the error code you're getting the very first hit will be a stack overflow
post with the answer you're looking for.
So that's a really fast way to get an answer.
Often I reply to Q&amp;A forums where Stack Overflow leaks.
Now you should also do a search on the Kewaunee forums in the course questions come up often more than
once and they'll already be answered for you in the question.
Answer forms by previous students.
You may also want to check out the Frequently Asked Questions lecture which is the next lecture right
after this one.
Now if all of that doesn't work for you you can always submit a new question in the question answer
forms please include details on what you've tried.
And a screenshot of your error code.
One quick tip before posting to the Q&amp;A forums please confirm that you're using our provided environment
which we set up in the course setup an installation lecture and that you've tried running our provided
notebooks in that provided environment.
Theoretically if you're running our provided notebooks directly in our provided environment you shouldn't
receive any errors whatsoever.
Often simple typos can cause errors especially for trying to type as you're watching videos.
So if you run the two steps above that will avoid any typos and your code should always run flawlessly.
Please keep in mind that we cannot help with your personal computer vision projects outside of the Course
questions of course material.
However this court chat channel is a great place to share your questions on your personal projects.
You can use the link in the automated welcome message to join our discourse server where we have that
student chat channel.
The automated welcome message that you receive when enrolling in this course also includes a link to
a YouTube video describing how to use and log in to the test server as far as the best way to approach
this course.
I recommend that you take a two pronged approach.
One is that you study the notebooks that contain the code used in every lecture and keep in mind that
organized in the same order they appear in the course of their all number and then the video and slides
from the actual course video platform.
Those usually contain explanatory concepts that can't really be shown through code so a lot of computer
vision.
It's a little hard to display impure code so we have some slides and some extra explanations in the
videos that you may not find in the code books.
So you want to take both approaches seriously as far as the Course notebooks those can be found as resource
links indiv AFAIK.
Lecture.
Keep in mind the very couple last sections on deep learning they do require some additional larger downloads
that aren't found in the zip file but the videos in that section of course will actually provide further
details on that data.
So you have to do a couple of extra downloads when you get to the deep learning section.
Just because there are some really large files to download Now keep in mind for that student chat channel.
The purpose of that chat channel to connect with students of other students and technical questions
related to the course material are best suited for the Q&amp;A forums.
OK so that's it.
Hope it didn't take too long.
And thank you so much for enrolling this course.
And I'm super excited to start your journey in computer vision.
We'll see you at the next lecture.